BU Records: Office of the President, Chancellor and President Emeritus: William Richardson White, Inclusive: 1936-1977, undated, Bulk: 1950-1969, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
BU Records: Office of the President, Chancellor and President Emeritus: William Richardson White
Inclusive: 1936-1977, undated, Bulk: 1950-1969, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
BU/142
Baylor University Office of the President
285 document boxes and 1 oversized boxes.
The William Richardson White papers contain correspondence, literary productions, photographs, clippings, and other materials related to White’s personal life and his role as Baylor University president and chancellor from 1948-1963.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Average.
Biography/Profile
William “Billy” Richardson White was born on his family's farm in Henderson County, Texas, on 1892 December 2. His parents, Gibson and Kittie Dorman White, died early in his childhood, and he was raised by his maternal grandmother, Missouri Ann White, in Frankston, Texas. In 1913, he entered Baylor University in Waco, but health issues forced him to transfer to Howard Payne College. It was at Howard Payne College that White met his first wife, Edna Woods. After graduating in 1917 with a Bachelor of Arts, both William and Edna White attended the Southwestern Baptist Theological Seminary. William served as the head of the seminary's department of missions after he received his masters and doctoral degrees.
Baptist Life
From a young age, White was active in the ministry, gaining his license to preach at 14. Throughout his life, White was a prominent member of the Baptist community. He served as Pastor of First Baptist Church in Greenville, Texas, from 1927-1928. When the Whites moved to Lubbock, William ministered at First Baptist Church. In 1929, White was elected as Executive Secretary of the Baptist General Convention of Texas. He served for three years. The Whites then relocated to Fort Worth in 1931, where they stayed for five years while William was pastor of Broadway Baptist Church.
The Whites moved to Oklahoma City in 1935, when William became the Director of Oklahoma Baptist University. After a number of years there, White served as President of Hardin-Simmons University for three years. During his presidency, the University and White became closer to the Baptist General Convention of Texas, resulting in White's presidency of the convention in 1943. His connection to the Baptist Sunday School Board came about the same time when he left Texas to become the editorial secretary in Nashville, Tennessee until 1945. The Whites then relocated to Austin, with William as the pastor of First Baptist Church until 1948.
Civic Life
White was a prolific supporter of several organizations and civic boards throughout his life, including his time as Baylor University president. One such organization was the Boy Scouts of America. White was involved with the Boy Scouts for decades as a scout leader.
White was on the Board of Regents of Bishop College, a historically Baptist African-American college founded in 1881 in Marshall, Texas, that relocated to Dallas in 1961. The college then closed in 1988 after facing financial and accreditation issues. White was also on the Board of Regents for Midwestern State University.
White was a Mason and involved with the Masonic community in Texas through the Baylor Lodge and the Scottish Rite. He also wrote Sunday school lessons for the Sunday School Board, a division of the National Baptist Convention. In addition, White authored many books, articles, pamphlets, and sermons.
Baylor University President 1948-1961
White was inaugurated as Baylor's 9th president in 1948. He served in that capacity until 1961. In his speech, White expressed his vision of reorienting faith into Baylor's mission. Baylor experienced tremendous growth during those years in the student population, the diversity of programs offered by the University, the physical campuses in Waco and Dallas, and the endowment fund.
White faced a devastating loss in his first year as president. His college sweetheart and wife since 1916, Edna, died after battling a long-term illness. Within a few years, White remarried Tennessee native Catherine West Tarwater. Baylor was very welcoming to the new first lady and her involvement with student life is fondly remembered.
White oversaw the university during a time of transition. Veterans were coming back home from World War II and using the G.I. Bill to attend college, which led to an influx of students. These students, along with their families, prompted White to lead efforts to construct new housing facilities. On the athletic side, a revitalization of Baylor football occurred with new hires and the construction of Floyd Casey Football Stadium, originally named Baylor Stadium.
Starting in 1959, White took on a development-focused role in the administration. This new position required him to travel for extended periods visiting potential donors and fostering relationships with other institutions in Baylor's name. The Board of Regents along with White made the decision that the Dean of the School of Law, Abner V. McCall, would be the Executive Vice President of Baylor. White and McCall maintained this split power until 1961; McCall became President of the University, and White took on the role of Chancellor.
Baylor University Chancellor 1961-1963 and President Emeritus 1963-1977
As Chancellor, White continued his development-focused role. After his travels, he returned to Baylor and soon began teaching religion courses. In 1970, his wife of 20 years, Catherine, died after battling cancer. White later remarried Odera Mohr and stayed with her until his death on 1977 March 24. He is buried in Oakwood Cemetery near Edna White in Waco.
Scope and Content
The W.R. White papers contain documents, audio-recordings, photographs, and visual materials relating to the personal and professional life of Baylor’s 9th president.
The first series, Correspondence, is the largest and runs from 1944-1977. It contains correspondence to and from White and includes a variety of topics including sports, religion, and politics.
The second series, Baylor University Records, contains institutional records like financial reports, trustee committee minutes, inauguration, and commencement materials.
The third series, Personal Papers, contains manuscripts and literary productions created by White, in addition to condolences and subject files White kept.
The fourth series, Memberships and Affiliations, documents the various civic and academic associations White had participated in throughout his life.
The final series is the audio and visual material from the collection. The recordings are sermons, most given by White. The photographs are productions from Baylor events and family photos.
Arrangement
Prior to current processing, the collection was arranged in titled folders with dates in boxes. Some folders were not dated. The collection had a container listing; however, the overall arrangement was hard to decipher due to multiple additions of boxes through the years. Original folder titles were kept in the latest round of processing.
Currently, the collection is arranged in five series: I. Correspondence, II. Baylor University Records, III. Personal Papers, IV. Memberships and Affiliations, and V. Audio and Visual Materials.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. BU/142. Acquired 1978-03-17
Related Resources
Related references
Bertsch, Amy. "Bishop College." East Texas History. Accessed 2017 May 9.
Find A Grave, Inc. “Catherine Jane West.” Memorial #71944183. Databases. Accessed 2017 May 9.
Find A Grave, Inc. “Edna V. White.” Memorial #96256694. Databases. Accessed 2017 May 9.
Find A Grave, Inc. “Dr. William Richardson ‘Billy’ White.” Memorial #94867504. Databases. Accessed 2017 May 9.
Herman, Jack and Peggy Hardman. "Bishop College." Handbook of Texas Online. Texas State Historical Association, 2015. Accessed 2017 May 9.
"History of Cub Scouting." Boy Scouts of America. Accessed 2017 May 9.
“William R. White.” Baylor University. Accessed 2017 May 9.
“William Richardson White.” Baylor University Libraries. Accessed 2017 May 9.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
White, W.R. (William Richardson) 1892-1977 -- Archives.
Subjects (Organizations)
Baptist General Convention of Texas -- Correspondence.; Baylor University -- Administration.; Baylor University -- Presidents -- Archives.; Baylor University -- Sports.; Baylor University. Office of the President -- Records and correspondence.
Subjects
Baptists -- Sermons.; College presidents -- Texas -- Waco -- Archives.
Genres
Financial records.; Minutes (Records); Open reel audiotapes.; Photographs.; Programs.; Reports.
- Correspondence, 1944-1977; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Average.
  Biography/Profile
  This series consists of the correspondences that White received throughout his tenure at Baylor University and beyond. This series is arranged into four subseries: I. General, II. People, III. Associations and Affiliations, and IV. Baylor University. The General subseries was originally filed by the senders’ last initial, and this arrangement was kept for the collection. The subjects discussed in this series vary, but most tie back to Baylor University, religion, and politics. The People subseries are correspondence that were filed by the full name of the sender. These folders have been arranged alphabetically. The Associations and Affiliations subseries is arranged by the organization and topic in alphabetical order. It differs from the Memberships and Affiliations series because of the lack of organizational records. The Baylor University subseries consists of invitations, scholarships, and various requests made to the president of the university. This subseries is arranged alphabetically. This subseries differs from the Baylor University Records series due to the lack of institutional reports presented within the folders.
  - General, 1944-1977; 1
    - 1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1953 and 1959, 1953, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - A, 1947-1952 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - A, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - A, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - A, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - A, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - A, 1959-1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - A, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - A (1 of 2), 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - A (2 of 2), 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - A, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - A, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - A, 1971-1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Ab, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Ab, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Ab, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Ab, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Ab, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Ab, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Ab, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Ad, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Ad, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Ad, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Ad, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Ad, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Ad, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Ad, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Ae-h, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Ae-h, 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Ae-h, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Ae-h, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Ai-l, 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Ai-l, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Ai-l, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Ai-l, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Ai-l, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Ai-l, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Ai-l, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Ai-l, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Am-o, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Am-o, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Am-o, 1953-1955 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Am-o, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Am-o (1 of 2), 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Am-o (2 of 2), 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Am-o, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Am-o, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - An-o, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Ap-s, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Ap-z, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Ap-z, 1953-1955 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Ap-z, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Ap-z, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Ap-z, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Ap-z, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Ap-z, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Articles Sent to Dr. White, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - B, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - B (1 of 3), 1951 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - B (2 of 3), 1951 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - B (3 of 3), 1951 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - B (1 of 4), 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - B (2 of 4), 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - B (3 of 4), 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - B (4 of 4), 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - B, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - B (1 of 4), 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - B (2 of 4), 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - B (3 of 4), 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - B (4 of 4), 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - B (1 of 2), 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - B (2 of 2), 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - B (1 of 3), 1963-1966, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - B (2 of 3), 1963-1966, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - B (3 of 3), 1963-1966, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - B, 1965-1967 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - B (1 of 2), 1966-1970 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - B (2 of 2), 1966-1970 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - B, 1971-1975 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Ba, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Ba (1 of 2), 1953 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Ba (2 of 2), 1953 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Ba (1 of 3), 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Ba (2 of 3), 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Ba (3 of 3), 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Ba, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Ba (1 of 2), 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Ba (2 of 2), 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Ba (1 of 3), 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Ba (2 of 3), 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Ba (3 of 3), 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Ba (1 of 2), 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Ba (2 of 2), 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Ba (1 of 2), 1958-1960 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Ba (2 of 2), 1958-1960 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Be, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Be, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Be, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Be-i, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Be-i, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Be-i, 1954-1956 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Be-i, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Be-i, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Bi, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Bi, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Bl, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Bl, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Bl, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Bl, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Bl, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Bl, 1957-1958 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Bl, 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Bl, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Bo, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Bo, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Bo, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Bo, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Bo, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Bo, 1957-1958 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Bo, 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Bo, 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Br, 1952-1953 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Br, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Br (1 of 2), 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Br (2 of 2), 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Br, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Br, 1956-1957 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Br, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Br (1 of 3), 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Br (2 of 3), 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Br (3 of 3), 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Br, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Bu, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Bu, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Bu (1 of 2), 1954-1955 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Bu (2 of 2), 1954-1955 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Bu-z, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Bu-z, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Bu-z, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Bu-z, 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Bu-z (1 of 2), 1959-1960 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Bu-z (2 of 2), 1959-1960 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - C (1 of 4), 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - C (2 of 4), 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - C (3 of 4), 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - C (4 of 4), 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - C (1 of 4), 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - C (2 of 4), 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - C (3 of 4), 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - C (4 of 4), 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - C (1 of 4), 1960-1963 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - C (2 of 4), 1960-1963 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - C (3 of 4), 1960-1963 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - C (4 of 4), 1960-1963 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - C, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - C (1 of 2), 1962-1964 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - C (2 of 2), 1962-1964 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - C (1 of 4), 1963-1966 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - C (2 of 4), 1963-1966 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - C (3 of 4), 1963-1966 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - C (4 of 4), 1963-1966 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - C, 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - C, 1966-1973 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - C, 1971-1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Ca, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Ca, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Ca, 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Ca, 1955-1957 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Ca, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Ca (1 of 2), 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Ca (2 of 2), 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Ca, 1956-1960 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Ca-g, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Cancelled Engagements, 1949-1950 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Ch, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Ch, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Ch, 1954-1955 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Ch, 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Ch-i, 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Ch-i (1 of 2), 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Ch-i (2 of 2), 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Ch-l, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Ch-l, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Cl, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Cl, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Cl, 1954-1955 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Cl, 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Cl, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Cl, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Co, 1951-1952 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Co, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Co (1 of 2), 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Co (2 of 2), 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Co (1 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Co (2 of 2), 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Co (1 of 2), 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Co (2 of 2), 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Co, 1957-1958 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Co (1 of 2), 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Co (2 of 2), 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Co (1 of 2), 1958-1960 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Co (2 of 2), 1958-1960 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Cr, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Cr, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Cr, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Cr, 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Cr, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Cr, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Cr-t, 1957-1958 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Cu, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Cu, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Cu-z, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Cu-z, 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Cu-z, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Cu-z, 1957-1958 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Cu-z, 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Cu-z, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - D, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - D, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - D, 1960-1966 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - D (1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - D (2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - D, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - D (1 of 2), 1961-1963 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - D (2 of 2), 1961-1963 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - D, 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - D, 1965-1969 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - D, 1967-1970 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - D, 1971-1975 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Da, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Da, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Da, 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Da, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Da, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Da, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Da, 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Da, 1959-1960 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - De, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - De, 1952-1955 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - De, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - De, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - De, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - De, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - De, 1959-1960 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - De-h, 1957-1958 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Di, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Di, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Di, 1954-1955 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Di, 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Di, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Di, 1957-1958 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Di, 1958-1959 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Di, 1959-1960 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Do, 1951-1952 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Do, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Do, 1954-1955 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Do, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Do, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Do, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Do, 1958-1959 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Do, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Dr-y, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Dr-y, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Dr-y, 1953-1955 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Dr-z, 1955-1956 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Dr-z, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Dr-z, 1957-1958 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Dr-z, 1958-1959 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Dr-z, 1959-1960 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - E, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - E, 1960-1961 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - E, 1961-1963 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - E, 1963-1964 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - E, 1964-1966 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - E, 1966-1969 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - E, 1971-1975 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Ea, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Ea, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Ea, 1954-1956 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Ea, 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Ea, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Eb, 1951-1952 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Eb, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Eb-c, 1954-1956 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Eb-c, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Eb-c, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Ed, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Ed, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Ed-h, 1954-1955 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Ed-h, 1954-1956 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Ed-h, 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Ed-h, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Ed-h, 1958-1959 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Ed-h, 1959-1960 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Ei, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Ei, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Ei-k, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Ei-k, 1954-1956 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Ei-k, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Ei-k, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Ei-k, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - El, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - El, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - El, 1954-1955 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - El, 1955-1956 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - El, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - El, 1958-1959 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - El, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - El-m, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Em, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Em, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Em, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - En, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - En, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - En-q, 1954-1955 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - En-q, 1955-1956 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - En-q, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - En-q, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - En-q, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - En-q, 1959-1960 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Engagements (1 of 3), 1947-1948 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Engagements (2 of 3), 1947-1948 (Box 24, Folder 29)